<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>ISO-8859-1</encodingKey>
    <letterhead>TCS_template</letterhead>
    <name>NCS Action Day - Ealing Blast From The Past Details</name>
    <style>freeForm</style>
    <subject>{!Contact.FirstName}, #BlastFromThePast is almost here!</subject>
    <textOnly>Hey Grads,

Thanks for signing up to to volunteer at Wimborne Court Care Home in Ealing! This email will let you know all the details for the day and what you need to bring.

Being part of #BlastFromThePast, you will be helping in a local care home and spend the day engaging with residents and taking part in a range of activities which they love to do but are in need of a bit of assistance. This can include teaching them about new technology, helping them write a letter to a relative, or even playing some games. You will also be making a creative collage of photos that will be taken on the day in the afternoon which the residents can have for a keep sake.

Being involved in this social action project means you have earned free tickets for the NCS Action Day celebration event taking place in Conway Hall after your project from 4pm to 8pm! You will be travelling from the care home to Conway Hall with your mentor.

This project will take place between 11am - 3pm. Please arrive at Wimborne Court for 10:45am so everyone is ready for 11am.

Address: Wimborne Court, Southwell Ave, Northolt, UB5 4EL

Please make sure to bring an oyster and a packed lunch as there are no shops nearby to buy food. Please also bring some money to put on your Oyster card as you will be getting the central line to Holborn where the celebration event will take place.

You will have 2 mentors on the day.
Isabella -  07785627449
Charlotte - 07908928651

These are the numbers you can contact on the day if you need to. If you have any questions regarding the day please free feel to email us on tcs.westlondon@the-challenge.org

Looking forward to seeing you all there!

The Core Grad Team</textOnly>
    <type>html</type>
</EmailTemplate>
